# THANH TAM, HUYNH



District 6, Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam +84 919 66 1368 tamhuynh.me@gmail.com

Skype: tamhuynh.0407

I have 5+ years of experience with Android. Worked as a Full-stack developer before help me understand the communication between frontend and backend and give a better result.

Coding convention and clean code are significantly important to me, especially if you are a leader. Your code is clean and clear, so does your teammates. Set a good example within the team to make us all grow.

About management ability: Keep the balance between business thinking and technical limitation is a problem for any product company. I have a developer background, with a proper business mindset help me understand both needs and find the solution, keeping all team on the target.

I want to work in a challenging environment where I could utilize my skills and use my knowledge to better the company's products

# PERSONAL INFORMATION

DOB: July 4th, 1994 in Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

Hometown: Ben Tre province, Viet Nam

Male, Married

Profile: <a href="http://www.tamhuynh.me">http://www.tamhuynh.me</a>
Blog: <a href="https://blog.tamhuynh.me">https://blog.tamhuynh.me</a>

Github: <a href="https://github.com/tamhuynhit">https://github.com/tamhuynhit</a>

StackOverflow: https://stackoverflow.com/users/3627898/tam-huynh

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tamhuynhit/

#### **EDUCATION**

#### HO CHI MINH UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE

Honors Program in Information Technology – Software Engineering

Thesis: 9.0

Graduate Year: Nov 2016 - Distinction

# **EXPERIENCE**

# Feb 2021 - Present 25INC

**Chief Product Manager/CEO Assistant** 

- Operate different activities for the company, both internal and external.
- Support CEO with operation strategy, product timeline
- Connect and Manage teams for effective cooperate

#### Jul 2016 – Present

#### **25INC**

**Android Lead developer/Product Manager** 

# Projects joined:

- gannha.com
- dkid.vn
  - Lead Mobile team with a team size of 5 members
  - Collaborate with different teams: from Development to Business, Marketing teams to bring products to reality
  - Find a way to manage and structure a complex one-page app
  - Join UI/UX discussion, apply user-oriented thinking

#### Feb 2016 - Feb 2017

# **EAST AGILE**

Python/Django developer

# Projects joined:

- Chinchilla (MySamsung backend)
- Samsung Data Science
  - We apply TDD, BDD patterns into our working process.
  - Learn how to communicate with customers, how to explain the development process to them, and keep them happy
  - We work in pair, which help me learn a lot, each project code is reviewed by the whole company
  - Coding convention, code quality, and product quality are our priorities. Always think further and keep the code maintainable for later developer

# Nov 2014 – Jun 2016 MICROSOFT STUDENT PARTNERS VIETNAM (MSP)

**Technical Evangelist** 

- Outstand over 60 other students to be a member of MSP.
- Trainer in WeSpeakCode campaign, Azure workshop of Microsoft Viet Nam.
- Launch 2 training courses on Microsoft technology with over 70 attendees.
- Running 2 team projects in Windows phone and Windows 10.

# Sept 2012 - Jun 2016 HO CHI MINH UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE

**Teaching Assistant, Student** 

- Teaching assistant in Android class for high-school students (AlLab program): Prepare teaching material, support students, host ending event.
- Member of Live Science club.

# OTHER ACHIEVEMENTS

| Mar 2015 | Won round 2 in Imagine Cup 2015 contest from Microsoft Viet  |
|----------|--------------------------------------------------------------|
|          | Nam.                                                         |
| Feb 2015 | Second round in Information Technology faculty's contest.    |
| 2012     | Achieved 2nd prize in Ho Chi Minh city for excellent student |
|          | contest (Informatics).                                       |

# SKILL

- Communication between different teams.
- Can work with UI tools like Adobe XD, Figma
- Be able to work with English material
- Work under pressure

# **INTERESTS**

- Working in the coffee shop
- Morning coffee
- Enjoy helping other developers on StackOverflow, help my teammates improve themselves